Massama Joël TASSIGA

Togolese | Lome, Togo | +228 92 74 37 49 mjtassiga@jumbafinder.com | LinkedIn | Skype ID: tassiga.joel

SUMMARY

As a motivated and proactive individual, I possess a wealth of experience in customer relations and marketing. Throughout my career, I have demonstrated my ability to handle challenging situations with ease and provide exceptional service to clients. Currently, I am pursuing an honors degree in Business Administration (BA), further enhancing my knowledge and skills in this field.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

University of People: Pasadena, CA - USA

2018 - 2022

BSc, Business Administration

The institution is committed to addressing significant challenges faced by society by providing students with innovative approaches to problem-solving through their coursework. Students work collaboratively to advance knowledge for meaningful contributions within the ideal framework of leadership.

Ghana Institute of Languages, Accra, Ghana

January 2019 - April 2019

Upper-intermediate level

Level B2 was to perform in English and get the highest skills to speak well in a professional career. This allows me to be connected with Anglophone communities.

Senior High School of Kpodzi (Lycee de Kpodzi) - Kpalime, Togo

September 2010 - July 2014

Relevant Coursework: Mathematical; Biology; Science physic, chemistry, English, French, History, Philosophy, Social Science

PROFESSIONAL WORK EXPERIENCE

CEO OF JUMBA March 2022 - January 2023

Jumba Company – Lomé, Togo(in-person)

- We Designed and maintained both corporate and client websites, using scripting languages.
- Assisted in Building beautiful user interfaces for clients.
- Built reusable codes and used a variety of markup languages to create web pages.

IT MANAGER September 2020

AFRICAN COMMUNITY CHANGERS - (remotely)

We Designed and maintained both corporate and client websites, using scripting languages.

- To make a significant change in African society by identifying problems and bringing adequate solutions
- Inspires African Youths in one way or the other to build the anxiety of becoming African Leaders

ENVIRONMENT CLUB: Earth Charter Youth

September 2012 - May 2014

High of Kpodzi, Togo (remotely)

- We Designed and maintained both corporate and client websites, using scripting languages.
- Trained 50+ students to take care of the environment in terms of using a plastic bottle
- Members' participation in **Plant For The Planet** campaign

IDEAS FOR US (TOGO) November 2014 - May 2015

Lomé, Togo(in-person)

- PreCop 20 Workshop in Lome with Jeune Verts TOGO and 350.org
- National Campaign and Walk for The Climate event participant

ABAC Sarl TOGO November 2020

Notsè, Togo - (in-person)

- Purchase of cereals
- Livestock and in logistic transport.

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

IT Manager, AFRICAN COMMUNITY CHANGERS

September 2020

enable the organization to design, coordinate, and manage its information systems.

Project manager, NGO LGD - TOGO (Ligue des Groupements pour le Developpement)

February 2019

leads the organization's purpose in planning and monitoring projects for the sustainable development of our community.

Area Supervisor, ECOCHANGE - TOGO

With my commitment and my love for nature, I was honored to be the area supervisor of this young community in my hometown for the protection of the environment.

Project Manager, ABAC Sarl: Agribusiness

November 2020

The project initially started with the purchase of cereals such as corn, soybeans, beans, groundnuts, and cashew nuts, and has since been padded to involve foreign partners for more focal points across the African continent.

SKILLS

- Event PlannerCritical thinking
- Front-End and Back-End Developer
- MS (Excel/Powerpoint)
- Digital Marketing
- Google Data analytics
- HTML/CSS/Javascript
- Project management
- Meta Social Media Marketing
- Google Digital Marketing and E-commerce

INTERESTS

- Software engineering
- React & React Native Developer
- Customer services
- Mobile App Development
- Meta Android & iOS Developer
- Cyber Security
- AI/ML
- Marketing

LANGUAGES

• Ewe - Native

- French Professional
- English Professional

- Kabye Native
- Russian Conversational

AWARD(S)

Award by Fred Swaniker, Founder of African Leadership University for completing African Rising Courses in May 2015, Leadership and Pan-Africanism courses.